

Dong Long, Cui

Full Stack Developer

I have in-depth knowledge of JavaScript and React concepts, excellent front-end coding skills, and a good understanding of progressive web applications, experience working on a complex project and have the ability to learn new technologies quickly.

CONTACT

- +1 603-217-5413
- stardev96610@gmail.com
- https://github.com/cooldev225

EDUCATION

2011 - 2014 Fudan University

 Bachelor Degree of Computer Science

SKILL

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

100%

React/Vue/Angular

95%

Node.js/PHP/Laravel/Express

90%

MySQL/MongoDB/Firebase

100%

AWS/Git/SEO

90%

Smart Contract/Web3.js/Solidity

90%

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

February 2021 to March 2022 Quantex - San Francisco, CA

- Worked across the full-stack of software development
- Created a skeleton loading system for React web app

Frontend Developer

May 2018 to January 2020 Worldie - Columbus, Ohio

- Convert from PHP + Bootstrap to MERN stack.
- Built an asynchronous web app for content creation.
- Managed git repositories alongside JIRA project management tool.
- Implemented encrypted search using a one way hash using a webbased cryptography library.

LANGUAGE



- English
- Chinese